DAYS!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
天下統一の道を行く王 嬴政(えいせい)のもと
By the decision of Ying Zheng, the king that wished to unite all of China,
the State of Qin began its invasion of the neighboring State of Wei.
秦国(しんこく)は 魏国(ぎこく)へと侵攻した
The enemy blocking their way is the legendary Great General, Lian Po.
立ちはだかる敵は
伝説の大将軍 廉頗(れんぱ)
Young generals take on this relentless battlefield in hopes of rendering great military achievements.
若き将たちは 大いなる武功を狙い
この苛烈な戦場に挑む
So then, I'm going to be taking your life, temporary Thousand-Man General.
（輪虎(りんこ)）…ということで
命をもらうよ 臨時の千人将君
Protect Lord Ben!
（番陽(ばんよう)）賁(ほん)さまを守れ！
ハハッ… 守れるかな？
Do you think you can?
（王賁(おうほん)）どけ
Get out of the way.
（番陽）ハッ… 賁さま…
Lord... Ben...
（王賁）俺がやる
I'll do it.
Xuan Feng's Scheme
The first formation is fighting a hard battle!
（伝令１）第１陣 苦戦中！
（伝令２）延比(えんぴ)隊 太雲(たいうん)隊 崩壊！
The Ting Bi Unit and Tai Yun Unit have been destroyed!
It now seems that General Tu Men has picked up a lance himself and taken the lead!
（伝令３）土門(どもん)将軍自ら矛を持って
先頭に立たれたもようです
（信(しん)）こ… こんなに早く
千人隊が２つも やられたのか…
Th-There were two Thousand-Man Generals taken out this quickly?!
H-Hold on a second.
（尾平(びへい)）ちょ… ちょっと待て
延比 太雲って ２つとも
今回 急造された千人隊じゃ…
Aren't the Ting Bi and Tai Yun Units two of the Thousand-Man Units that were just formed?
（慶(けい)）あっ！
（ざわめき）
Are they trying to say that a newly-formed Thousand-Man Unit can't hold water in actual battle?
（渕(えん)）実戦において―
急造した千人隊では
通用しないということなのか…
玉鳳(ぎょくほう)隊は どうなってる？
伝達係のおっさん！
How's the Yufeng Unit going?!
Hey, messenger guy!
（伝達係）
うん？ そんなことまで知るか！
Why the hell would I know something like that?!
誰じゃ 貴様！
Who the hell are you, anyway?!
（信）王賁…
Wang Ben...
One-on-one, eh?
一騎打ちか…
ハハッ… 興味ないな
That's no fun.
みんな…
Everyone, let's hurry and get this over with.
さっさと終わらせるよ
（輪虎隊兵たち）オーッ！
Wh-What?!
（兵士Ａ）な… なに？
Here they come!
（番陽）来るぞ！
（玉鳳隊兵たち）オーッ！
つ… 強い！
Th-They're strong!
Regardless of the lack of coordination among the unit or not...
隊の中の連携うんぬんの問題など
関係なく
this enemy is fantastically strong!
この敵は 恐ろしく強い！
It looks like unlike the other units, there's a good two or three hundred that are quite powerful.
この隊は ほかと違って
200～300ほど精鋭がいるみたいだね
'Course, even they're far less experienced than us.
まあ その彼らも こっちとは
経験の差が だいぶあるかな
何しろ 僕らは 初代趙国三大天(ちょうこく さんだいてん)と
秦国六大将軍の時代…
After all, I made it alive through the bloody age of the State of Zhao Three Great Devas
and the State of Qin Six Great Generals.
その修羅場をくぐり抜けてきた―
This is the unit of one of the Four Heavenly Kings directly under General Lian Po, the Lun Hu Unit.
廉頗将軍直属の四天王
輪虎隊だからね
One of Lian Po's Four Heavenly Kings?
（番陽）廉頗の四天王隊…
（王賁）関係ない
It does not matter.
No matter how strong the soldiers are,
兵が いかに強かろうと
隊長の貴様を討てば 隊は崩れ
if I slay you, the captain, your unit will collapse and the battle will be over.
それで終わりだ
（輪虎）そりゃそうだけど…
ハハッ… そうだな
Well, you've got a point there.
Yeah, I guess.
そんなに熱く求められたら
悪い気は しないや
If you're that intent on it, I won't think ill of you.
General Tu Men!
（副官）
土門将軍！ ムリはなさらず！
Do not push too hard!
（土門）分かっておる
I know!
I thought that by taking the helm myself, we would regain some momentum, but...
わし自ら先頭に立つことで
こちらの勢いは少々 取り戻したが
in an army of 8,000, losing 2,000 men so quickly is just too large a wound...
やはり 8,000の軍のうち―
2,000の隊が早々に崩れた痛手は
大きすぎる
General! Perhaps we should retreat temporarily and a plan a regrouping.
（副官）将軍 一度下がって
立て直しを図っては…
（土門）ならん！
No! Victory or defeat in this battle against vanguard units that started off with similar numbers
同数で
始まった この先鋒隊(せんぽうたい)の勝敗は―
will have a huge effect on both armies' morale!
両軍の全兵士の士気に大きく関わる
なんとしても
ここから戦局を覆すぞ！
We have to turn the tide of this battle, no matter what!
Come with me! We'll rouse the units that are in unfavorable positions!
（土門）劣勢の隊を鼓舞して回る
ついてまいれ！
（副官）ははっ！
Yes, sir!
Second formation! Prepare to sortie!
（栄備(えいび)）
第２陣 出撃用意！ 配置に就け！
Take your positions!
State of Qin General
Rong Bei
しかたない
第１陣の尻拭いに行くぞ
Oh well.
Let's go wipe the first formation's asses for them!
Feixin Unit! Xin! You there?!
飛信(ひしん)隊！ 信 おるか！
Uh, yeah!
（栄備）
第１陣の戦況は聞いてのとおりだ
You heard what state the first formation is in!
敵は 恐らく
急造千人隊を狙い撃ちにしている
The enemy is likely targeting newly-formed Thousand-Man Units!
So bear in mind, that means the one who's going to be targeted next is going to be your Feixin Unit!
つまり
今度も真っ先に狙われるのが―
お前の飛信隊と肝に銘じておけ！
ムハハッ… あっさり やられるなよ
ほかが迷惑する
So don't get killed really fast!
It'll cause problems for the rest of us!
ムハハハッ… 貴様の所もだ 常氾(じょうはん)
You, too, Chang Fan!
（常氾）ぎょ… 御意！
U-Understood!
望むところだ
Just... what I want.
（栄備）そっちは よいか？
You all ready?!
Let's get going!
そろそろ行くぞ
（兵士）ははっ！
Yes, sir!
Chu Shui, is our mounted unit ready?
楚水(そすい) 騎馬隊の準備はいいか？
…っし！
All right!
渕さんは…
How about Mr. Yuan?
Whenever you're ready!
（渕）いつでも！
…っし！
And Qiang Lei?
羌瘣(きょうかい)は…
ヘヘッ！ …っし！
All right!
Let's go!
いくぞ！
第２陣 出撃だ！
Second formation, sortie!
The second formation is charging.
（李充）第２陣 出ました
指揮官は栄備将軍 兵8,000
They are being directed by General Rong Bei.
They have 8,000 soldiers.
Among them, 2,000 are newly-formed Thousand-Man Units, the Feixin Unit and the Chang Fan Unit.
（李充）うち2,000は
飛信隊と常氾隊の急造千人隊です
ンンッ！
（輪虎）ウワッと…
Woah, there.
Ah! Lord Lun Hu can't get close to him?!
（輪虎隊兵）
あ… あの輪虎さまが近づけない
O-Our Lord Wang Ben sure is something.
（玉鳳隊Ｇ）さ… さすが王賁さま
（玉鳳隊Ｈ）ああ 一方的だ
Yeah. It's completely one-sided!
No... That's not the case...
（番陽）い… いや そうではない
先ほどから 賁さまは―
For a while now, Lord Ben has been thrusting all-out in a way he rarely shows even in actual battle.
実戦でも あまり見せないほどの
全力の突きを放っておられる
…にもかかわらず
And yet... that man still doesn't have a scratch on him!
あの男の体は
かすり傷ひとつ負っていない
I'm impressed.
驚いたな
これまで数え切れないほどの
槍使(やりつか)いと戦ってきたけど
I've fought with more lance-wielders than I can count,
but your skill trumps them all.
その中でも君は群を抜いているよ
That spearmanship... You're young, but it feels so adept.
その槍術(そうじゅつ) 若いのに熟練すら感じる
Of course.
当然だ
Relentless effort...
たゆまぬ努力…
槍においても 天賦の才を
持って生まれた賁さまだったが
Lord Ben was born with great skill for the lance,
but he never lets that go to his head.
決して
それに おごることはなかった
手の皮は破れ 血が噴き
その熱気に雪は昇華した
His skin would tear and spout blood.
And the snow would sublimate from his intensity.
荒武者のごとき修練を―
Lord Ben has trained like a savage since he was a child.
幼少のころより
積み重ねられた賁さまの槍は―
His lance has already reached the realm of mastery!
既に達人の域に達している！
（輪虎）まだ速くなる…
He's gotten even faster.
He's using it!
（玉鳳隊兵）出るぞ！
（玉鳳隊兵）これは…
This is...
龍指(りゅうし)！
Longzhi!
やっ …た！
He...
did it!
N-No!
いや！ は… 外した！
He missed!
（輪虎）ハァ…
初見なら
かわせたかどうか怪しいが
At first glance, I wasn't sure if I could dodge it or not...
But like I said before, I've fought a lotta lance users,
さっきも言ったとおり
多くの槍使いと戦って
and I've seen attacks similar to this one or two times.
似た技を
１～２度 見たことがあった
And also... did you know...
そして 知ってたかい？
（王賁）アア…
that one always leaves oneself open right after using big techniques?
（輪虎）大技の直後には
必ず隙が生じるって
（番陽）
なっ… 剣が！ いつ投げた？
Wha... When did he... throw his sword?!
（輪虎）この前の彼といい
秦国軍は 若手の有望株が多いな
With both you and that guy I met earlier, it looks like the State of Qin Army has a lot of promising young blood.
まあ しかし 君は運が悪かった
However, you had some bad luck.
槍が へし折られた…
He... broke my lance...
What power... this guy has...!
こやつ なんという力…
ンンッ！ ひとまず下がるぞ 玉鳳！
We're making a temporary retreat, Yufeng!
Bring Lord Ben back!
賁さまを後ろへ！
Sorry, you're not getting away.
逃がさないよ
（輪虎隊兵たち）オーッ！
（輪虎）ウワッ…
Don't make any hasty retreats.
（王賁）うかつに下がるな
背を打たれるだけだ
He only stabbed me back.
Lord Ben!
賁さま！
（王賁）この地にとどまって戦うぞ
We'll stay here and fight.
The next one... will not miss.
次は外さぬ
へえ…
この地響きは…
What's this shaking?
秦国軍の第２陣か！
The State of Qin Army's second formation?!
Here we go, vanguard!
今行くぞ 先鋒隊！
Lord Lun Hu! The enemy's second formation is coming!
（輪虎隊兵）輪虎さま
敵第２陣 来ます！ およそ8,000！
Their number is approximately 8,000!
接触します！
They're making contact!
General Lian Po, we must send reinforcements as well.
（白亀西(はくきさい)）
廉頗将軍 こちらも援軍を出さねば
No need.
（廉頗）必要ない
（白亀西）アア…
（廉頗）
不完全な軍を何度 送ろうと―
No matter how many imperfect armies they send, the same thing will only repeat.
Lun Hu
同じことの繰り返しよ
Thousand-Man General Chang Fan!
（常氾副官）常氾千人将
第１隊 分断されました！
The first unit has been divided!
The seventh unit has been annihilated!
（兵士１）第７隊 壊滅！
（兵士８）第８隊もです！
The eighth unit as well!
（常氾）
クッ… 第４隊を前に出せ！
Send the fourth unit forward!
（常氾副官）第４隊…
The fourth unit...
The fourth unit isn't here!
第４隊がいません！
（常氾）なんだと！
What?!
The strength of a unit on the battlefield
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
戦場において 隊の強弱は―
意識の統一と連携の精度に
大きく関わる
has a strong connection with having a united consciousness and precision of coordination.
Without that, a unit cannot fully demonstrate its powers of attack and defense.
それがなければ 隊は
攻守において 力を発揮できない
Enemy mounted soldiers incoming!
（兵士１）敵騎馬 来ます！
As shown by the Yufeng Unit's struggling,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
玉鳳隊ですら苦戦しているように
急造隊が実戦で ものになるのは
至難の業である
it is a monumentally difficult task for a hastily-formed unit to be successful in actual battle.
General Rong Bei, the Chang Fan Unit is in desperate straights!
（栄備軍副官）
栄備将軍！ 常氾隊 窮地です！
Send reinforcements!
応援を送れ！
クッ… やはりダメか…
As I thought, it's not going well, eh...?
How is the Feixin Unit doing?
飛信隊は どうしておる？
The Feixin Unit is similarly divided...
（栄備軍副官）
飛信隊も同じく分断され…
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）しかし その中にあって
不思議なことに ただひとつ…
But within all of that, one thing stood out...
The Feixin Unit alone released an intense light!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
飛信隊だけは強烈な光を放った
Go!
いけー！
何じゃ？
What?
Lord Lun Hu, there are cheers coming from the left side.
（輪虎の副官）
輪虎さま 左方で歓声が…
（輪虎）聞こえてるよ
I can hear it.
変な盛り上がりだな…
That's some odd excitement.
（玉鳳隊兵）歓声が
上がっているのは こちら側だ
It's our side raising those cheers.
Which unit is it?!
（玉鳳隊兵）どこの隊だ？
飛信隊か…
The Feixin Unit...?
Wh-What are these guys?
（黄）な… 何だ？ こいつら
隊として てんでバラバラ
As a unit, they're completely split apart.
特に 歩兵 騎兵との間には
連携のかけらもない
There's noticeably not a hint of coordination between the armored soldiers and the mounted soldiers.
So why don't they break down?
なのに なぜ崩壊しない？
なぜ これほど強い？
Why are they this strong?!
No. They're not simply divided...
いや 単にバラバラなだけじゃない
時折 この…
Sometimes they're...
ヒイッ！
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）飛信隊の活躍の裏には
ひとつのカラクリがあった
There was one trick behind the Feixin Unit's actions.
All right, next...
（楚水）では 次に
我々 騎馬隊が ここにいる場合
When we, the mounted units are here,
the foot soldiers should fall back this way and turn in this direction.
歩兵隊は
こちらを下げて こっちに旋回
At the same time, the unit will split in half and one group will join the mounted units.
同時に 隊を半分に割って
片側は騎馬についていく
What you need to be attentive of are here and here.
注意すべきは ここと ここ
If the enemy comes in here, you should immediately...
ここに敵に入られた場合は
すぐに…
I think we really should quit this after all, Chu Shui.
やっぱ やめよう 楚水
（楚水たち）うん？
We've got confidence in our physical strength,
（信）俺たちは
腕っぷしには自信はあるが
頭使うのは あんま得意じゃねえ
（尾平）うんうん
but weren't not so good at using our heads.
いきなり
連携技とか やろうとしてもムリだ
Suddenly trying to use coordination techniques like this ain't gonna work.
本番じゃ きっと大失敗する
We'll probably completely mess it up come the real battle.
I think it would actually be much better to fight individually.
それよりも逆に
個別に戦ったほうが まだマシだ
単独でも俺らは やれるし
We can do well even if it's alone.
郭備(かくび)隊のお前らも
問題はねえはずだ
You Guo Bei Units shouldn't have any problems with that, right?
し… しかし それでは
せっかく千人隊になった意味が…
B-But that would defeat the whole point of finally becoming a Thousand-Man-
No.
（楚水）いや
信どのの考えのほうが正しいと思う
I think Lord Xin's thinking is correct.
説明していながら 私も
これでは戦えない気がしていました
Even while I was explaining,
I got the impression that we would
not be able to fight this way.
Understood. For this war, we will forget all of this for now.
分かりました
この際 一度 全てを忘れましょう
And one more thing...
そして ただひとつ…
（信）うん？
There is one extremely simple and easy arrangement we should have while fighting as a Thousand-Man Unit.
（楚水）至極単純で簡単な決め事を
ひとつだけ―
千人隊として持って戦いましょう
（信）決め事？
Arrangement?
（楚水）それは…
That is...
The flag!
旗ーっ！
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）それは…
That is at any time and against any enemy,
いつ いかなるとき
いかなる敵と戦っていようと―
when a signal is given, to head towards the enemy that the captain, Xin, is currently targeting
合図があれば 隊長 信が
狙いを定めた敵に向かって―
1,000人一丸となって
襲いかかること！
and for all one thousand men to become one to attack it!
オオッ！ すげえ破壊力だ
敵の本隊が吹き飛んだぞ！
What awesome destructive power!
The enemy's main unit got blown away!
That's the first time that happened!
こんなの初めてだ！
（渕）信どの！
（信）ああ！
Lord Xin!
Yeah!
ヘヘッ… 確かに
今までには なかった破壊力だ
That was definitely destructive power we haven't had up 'til now.
If we can fight like this with just one strategy...
たったひとつの戦術で
こんだけ戦えるなら―
then we'll really become something awesome once we've got more experience!
練り込んだら
とんでもねえことになるぞ！
千人隊は！
A Thousand-Man Unit...
A Thousand-Man Unit has other strengths.
（楚水）千人隊の強みは
ほかにも ありますぞ
楚水！
Chu Shui!
周りをご覧なされ
（信）うん？
Please take a look around you.
（楚水）この飛信隊の攻勢が
ほかの隊にも伝わり
The Feixin Unit's aggression is circulating to the other units.
The entire State of Qin Army is starting to rally!
秦国軍全体が
盛り返し始めましたぞ！
（白亀西）れ… 廉頗将軍 これは…
G-General Lian Po.
What is this?!
フン…
よっしゃ！ ガンガンいけ！
All right! Keep it going!
Lord Lun Hu, the flow is shifting away!
輪虎さま 流れが向こうに…
（輪虎）妙だな
That's odd. I didn't expect the State of Wei Army's dominance to be overturned this easily.
こんなに あっさり魏国軍の優位が
ひっくり返されるなんて…
よっぽど 秦国の第２陣に
生きのいいのが いたのか…
I guess the State of Qin's second formation had a lot of pep to them.
よし しとめに行こうか
（副官）ははっ！
Okay, shall we go put an end to it?
Yes, sir!
な… 何じゃ？ このバカでかい音は
（ドラの音）
Wh-What's that incredibly loud sound?
うん？ 何だ何だ？
What the hell's that?!
（ドラの音）
（楚水）ドラの音…
A gong...?
（兵士）どうなってる？
合図だ
（番陽）合図？
It's a signal.
A signal?
チェッ… 早いよ
Dang. That was fast.
（ドラの音）
来るぞ
Here they come. The enemy's second formation.
敵の第２陣が…
General Lian Po, what's this sound?
（白亀西）廉頗将軍 この音は…
（廉頗）この廉頗の送る第２陣が
単なる増援だと思ったら大間違いだ
If you thought that the second formation that I, Lian Po, would send would be mere reinforcements,
then you would be mistaken.
ハッ…
（廉頗）見ておれ 白亀西
Take a look, Bai Guixi.
They're going to take the first battle.
緒戦は あやつが持っていくぞ
チッ… 何なんだよ！
来るなら とっとと来やがれ！
Damn, what is it?
If you're gonna come at us, then do it already!
（兵士）どこだ？
（兵士）どうなってる？
The sound... stopped?
音が止まった
（兵士）気をつけろ
（兵士）大丈夫か？
（兵士たち）ウワッ！
（信）煙？
Smoke?!
（じい）戦場が煙に包まれたぞ！
The battlefield's been covered by a smokescreen!
Are they using fire?!
火計(かけい)か？
（楽華(がくか)隊兵）いえ 火はありません
No! There's no fire!
とにかく
煙が戦場全体を覆っています
But for now, smoke is covering the entire battlefield.
（じい）
煙幕？ しかし これほど大規模な…
A smokescreen?
But something of this large a scale...
（楚水）信どの ご無事か？
（信）楚水か？
Lord Xin! Are you all right?!
Chu Shui?!
（楚水）やられました
視界を失い 皆 足が止まった
They've got us. They cut off our vision and stopped everyone's movement.
Shit. Just when we'd finally gotten some momentum...
（信）くそ！ せっかく
こっちが勢いに乗ってたときに！
That's likely the enemy's plan.
（楚水）敵の策略でしょう
フン…
こんなもので水を差しおって！
They think they can put a damper on us with something like this?! Naive!
甘いわ！
いっときの休戦で
戦況が変わると思うなよ！
Don't think for a moment that the state of the battle will change just because of a quick break in the action!
The moment this clears we'll start right back up!
晴れれば 再び…
（輪虎）
ハハッ… 怒ってる怒ってる
Oh, he sounds mad.
でも 本当に怖いのは ここからだよ
But the really scary part is only just starting.
（魏軍弓隊隊長）射(う)て！
Fire!
伏せろ！
（番陽）うん？
Get down!
クッ… バカな！ 正気か？ ヤツら
What?! Are those guys insane?!
自分らの味方ごと…
They're going to hit their own allies along with us!
魏国の兵の姿が… 消えている！
Wait, the State of Wei soldiers are... disappearing?!
Wait, they're coming from behind, too!
（玉鳳隊兵）後ろからも！
（玉鳳隊兵）なに？
What?!
The soldiers and the smoke are operating together.
煙と兵が連動している
Is the State of Wei Army intending to fight in all this?!
魏国軍は この中で戦う気か？
Let's change locations!
（楚水）場所を変えましょう！
敵は
我々がいた場所を記憶していて―
The enemy has memorized our position and are targeting it!
そこに射ち込んでいる！
この煙の中 場所さえ変えりゃ
ヤツらも見失うってか！
With all this smoke, will they lose track of us, too, if we just move?
よし 飛信隊 動くぞ！
（飛信隊兵たち）オーッ！
Okay, Feixin Unit, let's go!
We may encounter the enemy!
（楚水）敵に遭遇するやもしれぬ
気をつけろ！
Be careful!
（信）いけー！
Go!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）飛信隊だけでなく
玉鳳隊を含めた ほかの隊も―
It was not only the Feixin Unit. Other units, including the Yufeng Unit,
started moving to a different position.
位置を変えるべく動いた
魏国軍の弓隊から
その姿は見えておらず
For the State of Wei Army's bow unit, if they had to rely on the sound of footsteps alone, it was impossible to locate them.
足音だけで
その行方を探るのは不可能である
But...
しかし…
（番陽）な… なに？
What?!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）視界の失われた煙の中
Even with their vision cut off due to the smoke, the State of Wei Army's bow unit
魏国軍の弓隊は 正確に
秦国軍の部隊を追ってきたのである
was able to follow the State of Wei Army units precisely.
（刺さる音）
（去亥(きょがい)）ウッ！
Qu Hai!
去亥！
くそ… どうなってんだ？ こりゃ
Damn, what the hell's going on here?!
That's impossible!
そんなバカな…
（輪虎）
ハハッ… 大混乱だね やっぱり
Sounds like a huge panic. I expected as much.
緒戦の僕の出番は もうないかな？
But I guess the first battle isn't my moment to shine anymore.
After all, once they're caught by that man's techniques, there's no hope for escape.
何しろ…
あの人の術にハマったら
もう逃げられないからね
Lord Xuan Feng! There are currently no reports of any changes!
（副官）玄峰(げんぽう)さま 今のところ
変わった報告はありません！
（玄峰）分かっておるわい
いちいち言うな！
I know that!
You don't need to tell me every time!
歯応え なしじゃな フン…
What a soft response...
もういい あれを出せ
（副官）はぁ？ もうですか
Okay. Send that out.
Already, sir?!
いちいち聞き返すな！
早(は)よう出せ！
Stop talking back to me! Just do it!
Honestly, every kingdom is filled with nothing but idiots.
まったく
どこの国もバカばっかじゃ
Especially those State of Qin soldiers. Why are they so flustered by a strategy of this level?
特に秦国の兵…
この程度の計略で
何を泡食っておるか
フッ… つまらぬ
How dull. Is there nobody among them that uses their brain?
少しは頭の回るヤツは
おらんのかい
（鐘の音）
（羌瘣）なるほど
I see.
So that's what it is?
そういうことか
（信）
クッ… どこへ行きゃいいんだ？
Where do we go?!
（羌瘣）どこに行っても同じだ
No matter where you go, it'll be the same.
羌瘣！
Qiang Lei!
音を送って
こちらの位置を知らされている
They're making sounds to show where we are.
Sounds?
Feixin Unit
Sound Unit
Bow Unit
（信）音？
（羌瘣）この隊の周囲に
There are a number of units sending sound signals around this unit.
音の合図を送る兵が
潜んでいる
They're moving where we move
そいつらが
我々と共に動いて
弓隊に
位置を教えているんだ
and telling the bow unit where we are.
What?!
なに？
そ… そういえば
時々 騒音に紛れて鐘の音が…
N-Now that you mention it...
I've been hearing the sound of a bell among the noise once in a while.
Then if we just kill those guys, the arrows will stop coming, right?
じゃ そいつらをぶっ殺せば
矢は襲ってこねえんだな
But the enemy has probably thought of that as well.
（楚水）しかし
それは向こうも考えているはず
Even if we slay the soldiers sending the sounds, if they have a massive number of reserves,
音を送る兵を斬っても
その予備が無数にいるとしたら
there will be no end to it.
キリがありません
それよりもマズイのは
この煙の中―
And the more pressing matter is that in this smoke,
我々は既に大半の味方の行方を
見失ったのに対し
we've lost track of the majority of our allies
魏国の兵は 敵味方の位置を
把握しているということ
while the State of Wei's soldiers have a grasp of where all of their enemies and allies are.
バラバラになった小隊は
個別に抹殺されていきます
All of the small, split-up units are being wiped out individually.
ここは一度 煙の外まで出て…
I think we should exit the smoke for the moment...
Now what's this sound signaling?!
（渕）クッ… この音…
今度は何の合図だ？
No, wait a sec!
いや ちょっと待て！
これは合図じゃねえ
This isn't a signal!
Th-This sound. Don't tell me it's...
こ… この音って まさか あの…
Y-Yeah...
（澤圭(たくけい)）は… はい！
This ain't good.
（沛浪(はいろう)）マズイ！
The State of Wei's armored chariots!
魏国の装甲戦車だ！
（戦車兵Ａ）ハアーッ！
しまった！ そこの歩兵 逃げろ！
Dammit!
Foot soldiers over there, run!
Damn, now chariots of all things...
（信）
クッ… よりによって戦車が…
Protect the captain!
（楚水）隊長を守れ！
俺は いい！
それよりも歩兵たちを！
I'll be fine!
Focus on the foot soldiers!
ンンッ… この煙に戦車…
Chariots in this smoke...
What do we do?! How do we...?!
どうする？ どうやって…
Xin.
（羌瘣）信！
（信）ああ？
ひとつだけ…
（信）うん？
Just one.
I have one plan.
ひとつだけ策がある
Preview
The Feixin Unit's
Counterattack
End